(birds chirping)
(gentle music)
♪ Three little birds sat on my window ♪
♪ And they told me I don't need to worry ♪
♪ Summer came like cinnamon, so sweet ♪
♪ Little girls, double-dutch
on the concrete ♪
♪ Maybe sometimes ♪
♪ We got it wrong, but it's all right ♪
♪ The more things seems to change ♪
♪ The more they stay the same ♪
♪ Ooh, don't you hesitate ♪
♪ Girl, put your records on ♪
♪ Tell me your favorite song ♪
♪ You go ahead, let your hair down ♪
♪ Sapphire and faded jeans ♪
♪ I hope you get your dreams ♪
♪ Just go ahead, let your hair down ♪
♪ You're gonna find yourself
somewhere, somehow ♪
♪ Blue as the sky, sunburnt and lonely ♪
♪ Sipping tea in a bar by the road side ♪
♪ Just relax, just relax ♪
♪ Don't you let those
other boys fool you ♪
♪ Gotta love that Afro hairdo ♪
♪ Maybe sometimes ♪
♪ We feel afraid, but it's all right ♪
♪ The more you stay the same ♪
♪ The more they seem to change ♪
♪ Don't you think it's strange ♪
♪ Girl, put your records on ♪
♪ Tell me your favorite song ♪
♪ You go ahead, let your hair down, girl ♪
♪ Sapphire and faded jeans ♪
♪ I hope you get your dreams ♪
♪ Just go ahead, let your hair down ♪
♪ You're gonna find yourself
somewhere, somehow ♪
♪ Just more than I could take ♪
♪ Pity for pity's sake ♪
♪ Some nights kept me awake ♪
♪ I thought that I was stronger ♪
♪ When you gonna realize ♪
♪ That you don't even
have to try any longer ♪
♪ Do what you want to ♪
♪ Girl, put your records on ♪
♪ Tell me your favorite song ♪
♪ You go ahead, let your hair down ♪
♪ Go let your hair down ♪
♪ Sapphire and faded jeans ♪
♪ I hope you get your dreams ♪
♪ Hope you get your dreams ♪
♪ Just go ahead, let your hair down ♪
♪ Baby, let your hair down ♪
♪ Girl, put your records on ♪
♪ Tell me your favorite song ♪
♪ You go ahead, let your hair down ♪
♪ Sapphire and faded jeans ♪
♪ I hope you get your dreams ♪
♪ Just go ahead, let your hair down ♪
♪ Ooh, you're gonna find
yourself somewhere ♪
♪ Somehow ♪